Guide to the Religious Education Association Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Publications, Series VI
  - Pamphlets
    - "Legal and Other Critical Issues of Religion in Public and Higher Education," ed. by H. Wornom, 1959 (Box 88, Folder 1053)
    - "Religion, Theology, and Public Higher Education: A California Study", 1962 (Box 88, Folder 1054)
    - Research supplement to Religious Education: Review of Recent Research Bearing on Religious and Character Formation; Lists of publications, 1962 (Box 88, Folder 1055)
- Research, Series VII
  This Series is divided into the following sections and sub-sections:
  Research activity prior to 1954 (1922-1940, n.d.)
  Research Committee (1954-1981): Correspondence, Minutes and memos
  Lilly Endowment Five-Stage Project (1950-1974): Survey of Research in Religion and Character Education, Survey on Problems in Religious Education, 1959 Consultations, 1961 Workshop, Research Department, Lilly Post-Doctoral Empirical Research Training Fellowships
  Research in Religious Development Handbook
  Faith in the Adult Life Cycle
  - Research Activity Prior to 1954
    - Correspondence, memos, reports, 1922-1928 (Box 89, Folder 1056)
    - Reports of Character Education Research Conferences held at the Chicago Theological Seminary, 1928, 1929 (Box 89, Folder 1057)
    - Correspondence, memos, reports, 1930-1940 (Box 89, Folder 1058)
    - Samples of tests and measurements related to religious education (Box 90, Folder 1059-1061)
  - Research Committee
    - Correspondence of Herman Wornom, 1954-1967 (Box 90, Folder 1062-1067)
    - Correspondence of Boardman Kathan, 1970-1977, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 1068)
    - Minutes, memos, 1954-1959 (Box 90, Folder 1069-1071)
    - Minutes, memos, 1960-1961 Sep (Box 91, Folder 1072-1073)
    - Subcommittee to Consider Strategy and Steps to be taken by the Religious Education Association to Foster Research in the Future, 1961 Nov (Box 91, Folder 1074)
    - Subcommittee to Select a Director of Research, 1963-1964 (Box 91, Folder 1075-1077)
    - Minutes and memos, 1965-1981 (Box 91, Folder 1078-1085)
  - Lilly Endowment, 5-stage project
    - Survey of Research in Religion and Character Education
      - Survey of Research in Religion and Character Education (Box 92, Folder 1086)
    - Survey on Problems in Religious Education (1959)
      - Summary Reports (Box 92, Folder 1087-1088)
      - Numbered responses - Part I (Box 92, Folder 1089)
      - Numbered responses - Part II (Box 92, Folder 1090)
      - Responses - A-F (Box 92, Folder 1091)
      - Responses - G-K (Box 92, Folder 1092)
      - Responses - L-N (Box 92, Folder 1093)
      - Responses - O-Z (Box 92, Folder 1094)
      - Suggested respondents (Box 92, Folder 1095)
    - 1959 Consultations
      - Planning Correspondence, 1959 Jan-Apr (Box 93, Folder 1096)
      - Planning Correspondence, 1959 May-Jun (Box 93, Folder 1097)
      - Planning Correspondence, 1959 Jul-Dec (Box 93, Folder 1098)
      - Planning for Panel (Box 94, Folder 1099)
      - Background papers: Blizzard - Loomis (Box 94, Folder 1100)
      - Background papers: Mowrer (Box 94, Folder 1101)
      - Panel Transcripts - First Conference, 1959 Jun 13, 14 (Box 94, Folder 1102)
      - Panel Transcripts - Second Conference, 1959 Jul 4, 5 (Box 94, Folder 1103-1104)
      - Panel Transcripts - Third Conference, 1959 Jul 18, 19 (Box 95, Folder 1105-1106)
      - Draft Report - First Conference, 1959 Jun 13, 14 (Box 95, Folder 1107)
      - Draft Report - Second Conference, 1959 Jul 4, 5 (Box 95, Folder 1108)
      - Draft Report - Third Conference, 1959 Jul 18, 19 (Box 95, Folder 1109)
      - Final Report of Conferences (Box 95, Folder 1110)
      - "Highlights of Recommendations for Research" (condensed version of conference reports) (Box 95, Folder 1111)
      - Reactions to "Highlights of Recommendations for Research": Summaries (Box 96, Folder 1112)
      - Reactions: American Baptist (Box 96, Folder 1113)
      - Reactions: Catholic (Box 96, Folder 1114-1115)
      - Reactions: Jewish (Box 96, Folder 1116)
      - Reactions: Lutheran (Box 96, Folder 1117)
      - Reactions: Methodist (Box 96, Folder 1118)
      - Reactions: Presbyterian Church in the United States (Box 96, Folder 1119)
      - Reactions: Presbyterian seminary professors (Box 96, Folder 1120)
      - Reactions: Protestant Episcopal (Box 96, Folder 1121)
      - Reactions: Southern Baptist (Box 96, Folder 1122)
      - Reactions: United Christian Missionary Society (Box 96, Folder 1123)
      - Reactions: United Church of Christ (Box 96, Folder 1124)
      - Reactions: United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A. (Box 96, Folder 1125)
      - Reactions: YMCA (Box 96, Folder 1126)
      - Reactions: Miscellaneous associations (Box 96, Folder 1127)
      - Reactions: Miscellaneous individuals (Box 96, Folder 1128-1129)
    - 1961 Workshop
      - Planning and promotion: Correspondence with Lilly Endowment, 1959 (Box 96, Folder 1130)
      - Planning and promotion: Minutes of Workshop - Executive Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 96, Folder 1131)
      - Planning and promotion: Announcements, 1960-1961 (Box 96, Folder 1132-1133)
      - Planning and promotion: Re. Workshop Director (Box 96, Folder 1134)
      - Planning and promotion: Correspondence of Workshop Director, Stuart Cook (and his secretary), 1960-1962 (Box 96, Folder 1135-1136)
      - Planning and promotion: Miscellaneous notes and correspondence of Herman Wornom, 1960-1961 (Box 96, Folder 1137)
      - Planning and promotion: Accommodations at Cornell, 1960-1962 (Box 97, Folder 1138)
      - Planning and promotion: Suggested consultants and participants (Box 98, Folder 1139-1141)
      - Planning and promotion: Invitations to research consultants (Box 98, Folder 1142)
      - Planning and promotion: Invitations to theological consultants (Box 98, Folder 1143)
      - Miscellaneous inquiries regarding research - correspondence of Herman Wornom, 1960-1962 (Box 98, Folder 1144)
      - Applicants - A (Box 98, Folder 1145)
      - Applicants - B (Box 98, Folder 1146)
      - Applicants - C-E (Box 98, Folder 1147)
      - Applicants - F-H (Box 98, Folder 1148)
      - Applicants - I-L (Box 98, Folder 1149)
      - Applicants - M-N (Box 98, Folder 1150)
      - Applicants - O-R (Box 98, Folder 1151)
      - Applicants - S (Box 99, Folder 1152)
      - Applicants - T - Z (Box 99, Folder 1153)
      - List of those selected (Box 99, Folder 1154)
      - Communications to participants, 1961 (Box 99, Folder 1155)
      - Paper sent to participants ("Experimental Designs for Research on Teaching" by Campbell and Stanley) (Box 99, Folder 1156)
      - Bibliographies Made Available (Box 99, Folder 1157)
      - Participants: Azneer (Box 99, Folder 1158)
      - Participants: Bischoff (Box 99, Folder 1159)
      - Participants: Birmingham (Box 99, Folder 1160)
      - Participants: Boehm (Box 99, Folder 1161)
      - Participants: Bowers (Box 99, Folder 1162)
      - Participants: Brewer (Box 100, Folder 1163)
      - Participants: Cooke (Box 100, Folder 1164)
      - Participants: Coville (Box 100, Folder 1165)
      - Participants: Daniel (Box 100, Folder 1166)
      - Participants: Douglas (Box 100, Folder 1167)
      - Participants: Draper (Box 100, Folder 1168)
      - Participants: Duling (Box 100, Folder 1169)
      - Participants: Feifel (Box 100, Folder 1170)
      - Participants: Francis, Sister M.T. (Box 100, Folder 1171)
      - Participants: Gladden (Box 100, Folder 1172)
      - Participants: Glasner (Box 100, Folder 1173)
      - Participants: Golter (Box 100, Folder 1174)
      - Participants: Graebner (Box 100, Folder 1175)
      - Participants: Grinder (Box 100, Folder 1176)
      - Participants: Ham (Box 100, Folder 1177)
      - Participants: Harte (Box 100, Folder 1178)
      - Participants: Hostetler (Box 101, Folder 1179)
      - Participants: Johnson, C. (Box 101, Folder 1180)
      - Participants: Johnson, R. (Box 101, Folder 1181)
      - Participants: Judy (Box 101, Folder 1182)
      - Participants: Keegan (Box 101, Folder 1183)
      - Participants: Kemp (Box 101, Folder 1184)
      - Participants: Kuhinka (Box 101, Folder 1185)
      - Participants: Kurtz (Box 101, Folder 1186)
      - Participants: Liu (Box 101, Folder 1187)
      - Participants: McDade (Box 101, Folder 1188)
      - Participants: McNair (Box 101, Folder 1189)
      - Participants: O'Donovan (Box 101, Folder 1190)
      - Participants: Proctor (Box 101, Folder 1191)
      - Participants: Reece (Box 101, Folder 1192)
      - Participants: Roberts (Box 101, Folder 1193)
      - Participants: Royce (Box 101, Folder 1194)
      - Participants: Sibley (Box 102, Folder 1195)
      - Participants: Sie (Box 102, Folder 1196)
      - Participants: Siegman (Box 102, Folder 1197)
      - Participants: Slusser (Box 102, Folder 1198)
      - Participants: Solomon (Box 102, Folder 1199)
      - Participants: Spickler (Box 102, Folder 1200)
      - Participants: Spoerl (Box 102, Folder 1201)
      - Participants: Spitzer (Box 102, Folder 1202)
      - Participants: Shippey (Box 102, Folder 1203)
      - Participants: Tamney (Box 102, Folder 1204)
      - Participants: Toch (Box 102, Folder 1205)
      - Participants: Union College Team (Box 102, Folder 1206)
      - Participants: United Presbyterian Team (Box 102, Folder 1207)
      - Participants: Vernon (Box 102, Folder 1208)
      - Participants: Whiteman (Box 102, Folder 1209)
      - Participants: Williams (Box 102, Folder 1210)
      - Participants: Wrightsman (Box 102, Folder 1211)
      - Participants: Woods, Sister F.J. (Box 102, Folder 1212)
      - Participants: Wyckoff (Box 102, Folder 1213)
      - Work Group I (Box 103, Folder 1214)
      - Work Group II (Box 103, Folder 1215)
      - Work Group III (Box 103, Folder 1216)
      - Work Groups IV, V (Box 103, Folder 1217)
      - 1961 Workshop: Work Groups VI, VII (Box 103, Folder 1218)
      - 1961 Workshop: Work Groups VIII,IX, X (Box 103, Folder 1219)
      - Recommendations of Work Groups (Box 103, Folder 1220 -1221)
      - Recommendations of Work Groups; Transcription of last session of Workshop (Box 103, Folder 1222)
      - List of research papers prepared for Workshop (Box 103, Folder 1223)
      - Research projects: Barton (Box 103, Folder 1224-1225)
      - Research projects: Bronfenbrenner (Box 104, Folder 1226)
      - Research projects: Campbell (Box 104, Folder 1227)
      - Research projects: Hiltner, Rogers (Box 104, Folder 1228-1229)
      - Research projects: Hoffman (Box 104, Folder 1230)
      - Research projects: Ligon team - Part I (Box 104, Folder 1231)
      - Research projects: Ligon team - Part II (Box 104, Folder 1232)
      - Research projects: Ligon, Koppe, Smith (Box 104, Folder 1233)
      - Research projects: Shlien (Box 104, Folder 1234)
      - Research projects: Vayhinger (Box 104, Folder 1235)
      - Research projects: Withey (Box 104, Folder 1236)
      - Evaluations: Summaries (Box 105, Folder 1237)
      - Evaluations: Statements, letters from participants (Box 105, Folder 1238)
      - Evaluations: Reports in journals (Box 105, Folder 1239)
      - Post-workshop publication: Research Plans in the Fields of Religion, Morality and Values, 1962 (Box 105, Folder 1240-1244)
      - Follow-up: Financial matters, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 1245)
      - Follow-up: Reports of research progress, 1962 (Box 105, Folder 1246)
      - Follow-up: Reports of research progress, 1963, 1966 (Box 106, Folder 1247-1249)
      - Follow-up: Birmingham paper, 1966 (Box 106, Folder 1250)
      - Follow-up: Graebner, Grinder papers, 1966 (Box 106, Folder 1251)
      - Follow-up: Wrightman paper, 1966 (Box 106, Folder 1252)
      - Notebook documenting the Workshop; Photographs taken at Workshop (Box 107, Folder 1253)
    - Research Department
      - Proposals re. setting up department (see also records of Research Committee, Subcommittee to Select a Director of Research) (Box 108, Folder 1254)
      - Individuals considered for position of Director of Research Department (Box 108, Folder 1255-1256)
      - Selection of Merton Strommen as Director of Research Department (Box 108, Folder 1257)
      - Correspondence of Merton Strommen, 1964 Feb-Jun (Box 108, Folder 1258)
      - Correspondence of Merton Strommen, 1964 Jul-Dec (Box 108, Folder 1259)
      - Correspondence of Merton Strommen, 1965 Jan-Mar (Box 108, Folder 1260)
      - Correspondence of Merton Strommen, 1965 Apr-Jun (Box 108, Folder 1261)
      - Correspondence of Merton Strommen, 1965 Jul-Oct (Box 108, Folder 1262)
      - Correspondence of Merton Strommen, 1965 Nov-Dec (Box 108, Folder 1263)
      - Correspondence of Merton Strommen, 1966 Jan (Box 108, Folder 1264)
      - Correspondence of Merton Strommen, 1966 Feb-Apr (Box 108, Folder 1265)
      - Correspondence of Merton Strommen, 1966 May-Jun (Box 109, Folder 1266)
      - Correspondence of Merton Strommen, 1966 Jul-Nov (Box 109, Folder 1267)
      - Correspondence of Merton Strommen, 1967 Jan-May (Box 109, Folder 1268)
      - Correspondence of Merton Strommen, 1967 Jun-Dec (Box 109, Folder 1269)
      - Correspondence of Merton Strommen, 1968 Jan-Jul (Box 109, Folder 1270)
      - Correspondence of Merton Strommen, 1968 Aug-Dec (Box 109, Folder 1271)
      - Correspondence of Merton Strommen, 1969-1971 (Box 109, Folder 1272)
      - Correspondence of Herman Wornom, other than to/from Strommen, 1965-1968 (Box 109, Folder 1273)
      - Strommen Files: Writings of Strommen, 1961-1965 (Box 109, Folder 1274-1275)
      - Strommen Files: Re. Human Relationship Course (Box 109, Folder 1276)
    - Lilly Post-Doctoral Empirical Research Training Fellowships
      - Correspondence with Lilly Endowment, 1961-1965 (Box 110, Folder 1277-1278)
      - (incl. 10-year report), 1974 (Box 110, Folder 1279)
      - Administrative files, 1965-1966, 1974 (Box 110, Folder 1280-1281)
      - Financial, 1964-1968 (Box 110, Folder 1282)
      - Announcements/application forms, 1965-1966, n.d. (Box 110, Folder 1283)
      - Proposed applicants/inquiries, 1963-1966 (Box 110, Folder 1284-1286)
      - Proposed applicants/inquiries, 1967-1974 (Box 111, Folder 1287-1288)
      - Rejected applications, 1967 (Box 111, Folder 1289)
      - Recipients of fellowships: Joyce H.E. Bailey (Box 111, Folder 1290)
      - Recipients of fellowships: Milo Brekke (Box 111, Folder 1291)
      - Recipients of fellowships: John D. Cato (Box 111, Folder 1292)
      - Recipients of fellowships: Burton Cohen (Box 111, Folder 1293)
      - Recipients of fellowships: Roger Desmarais (Box 111, Folder 1294)
      - Recipients of fellowships: Roy W. Fairchild (Box 111, Folder 1295)
      - Recipients of fellowships: Warren J. Hartman (Box 111, Folder 1296)
      - Recipients of fellowships: Helen Khoobyar (Box 112, Folder 1297)
      - Recipients of fellowships: James M. Lee (Box 112, Folder 1298)
      - Recipients of fellowships: Robert T. O'Gorman (Box 112, Folder 1299)
      - Recipients of fellowships: Paul M. Lederach (Box 112, Folder 1300)
      - Recipients of fellowships: Paul B. Maves (Box 112, Folder 1301-1302)
      - Recipients of fellowships: Charles F. Melchert (Box 112, Folder 1303)
      - Recipients of fellowships: Allen J. Moore (Box 112, Folder 1304)
      - Recipients of fellowships: Catherine H. Smith (Box 112, Folder 1305)
      - Recipients of fellowships: Samuel Southard (Box 112, Folder 1306)
      - Recipients of fellowships: Theodore W. Thompson (Box 112, Folder 1307)
      - Recipients of fellowships: D. Campbell Wyckoff (Box 112, Folder 1308-1309)
  - Research in Religious Development Handbook
    - Administrative files, 1966-1976 (Box 113, Folder 1310-1317)
    - Introductory material (Box 114, Folder 1318)
    - Chapters 1-11 (Box 114, Folder 1319- 1326)
    - Chapter 12-21 (Box 115, Folder 1327- 1335)
    - Manuscript Review Conferences, 1967 (Box 116, Folder 1336)
    - Papers from Wrightsman and Koppe, 1970, 1971 (Box 116, Folder 1337)
    - Survey re. marketing of paper copy, 1970 (Box 116, Folder 1338)
    - Appraisal conferences, 1970-1971 (Box 116, Folder 1339-1340)
    - Reviews, interpretation (Box 116, Folder 1341-1342)
  - Faith in the Adult Life Cycle
    - Record s, 1976-1980 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1343-1345)
    - Records, 1980 May- 1982 May (Box 117, Folder 1346-1355)
- Religion and Higher Education, Series VIII
  Pre-Wornom era activity
  Wornom era files: General R.E.A. activity; Regional Round Tables; Planning Commission on the Study of the Place of Religion in the Curricula of State Universities; Other material re. religion and higher education (Specific conferences, projects, organizations, Religion programs at specific institutions, General articles)
  Kathan era files
  - Pre-Wornom era activity
    - Pre-Wornom era activity, 1939-1948, n.d. (Box 118, Folder 1356)
  - Wornom era files
    - General R.E.A. activity
      - Committee records, 1954-1956 (Box 118, Folder 1357)
      - Correspondence, 1953-1959 (Box 118, Folder 1358-1365)
    - Regional Round Tables
      - General: Announcements, proposals, issues raised, 1954-1955 (Box 118, Folder 1366)
      - General correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 118, Folder 1367)
      - General correspondence, 1955 (Box 118, Folder 1368)
      - New York Roundtable on "The Responsibility of Higher Education for Judeo-Christian Values in American Culture": Program, proposals, issues raised, 1954 Nov 26, 27 (Box 118, Folder 1369)
      - New York Roundtable: Attendance lists, invitations, responses (Box 118, Folder 1370)
      - New York Roundtable: Correspondence with participants, appraisals (Box 118, Folder 1371)
      - Chicago Regional Round Table on "The Responsibility of Higher Education for Judeo-Christian Values in American Culture": Program, proposals, issues raised (Box 119, Folder 1372)
      - Chicago Regional Round Table: Notes on proceedings (Box 119, Folder 1373)
      - Chicago Regional Round Table: Attendance lists, invitations, responses (Box 119, Folder 1374-1377)
      - Chicago Regional Round Table: Correspondence with participants, appraisals, 1955 Feb 11,12 (Box 119, Folder 1378)
      - Minnesota Regional Round Table (see below: Planning Commission on the Study of the Place of Religion in the Curricula of State Universities), 1955 Apr 25-27
      - Pittsburgh Round Table on "Religion and Education for Professional Responsibility
      - Pittsburgh Round Table: Attendance list, correspondence, 1955 Nov 18, 19 (Box 119, Folder 1379)
      - Pittsburgh Round Table: Report (Box 119, Folder 1380)
      - Boston Regional Round Table on "The Responsibility of Higher Education for the Judeo-Christian Heritage in American Culture": Program, report of proceedings, 1957 Nov 16, 17 (Box 119, Folder 1381)
      - Boston Regional Round Table: Attendance, proposed participants (Box 119, Folder 1382)
      - Boston Regional Round Table: Attendance list, invitations, responses (Box 120, Folder 1383)
      - Boston Regional Round Table: Post-round table correspondence (Box 120, Folder 1384)
    - Planning Commission on the Study of the Place of Religion in the Curricula of State Universities (co-sponsored by R.E.A. and University of Minnesota)
      - Preliminary planning meetings, 1953-1954 (Box 120, Folder 1385)
      - Program, 1955 Apr (Box 120, Folder 1386)
      - Attendance, 1955 Apr (Box 120, Folder 1387)
      - Minutes of business section committee and workshop reports, 1955 Apr (Box 120, Folder 1388)
      - Papers presented, 1955 Apr (Box 120, Folder 1389)
      - Evaluations, 1955 Apr (Box 120, Folder 1390)
      - Executive (Continuation) Committee meetings, 1955-1958 (Box 120, Folder 1391-1394)
      - Sub-committee meetings: Committee on Study of Administrative and Curricula Patterns for Dealing with Instruction in Religion in State Universities, 1958 (Box 120, Folder 1395)
      - Sub-committee meetings: Committee on Study of Need, Supply and Training of Instructors in Religion for State Universities, 1958 (Box 120, Folder 1396)
      - Correspondence, 1953 Dec-1958 Jun (Box 121, Folder 1397-1411)
      - Correspondence, 1958 Jul-1959 (Box 122, Folder 1412-1414)
      - Proposals, projects resulting from Commission (see also: Series VI, Publications: "Legal and Other Critical Issues of Religion in Public and Higher Education", ed. by H.E. Wornom), 1958, n.d. (Box 122, Folder 1415)
      - Financial records, 1955-1958 (Box 122, Folder 1416)
    - Other material re. religion and higher education
      - Specific conferences, projects, organizations
        - Association for Higher Education, 12th National Conference, Chicago, 1957 (Box 122, Folder 1417)
        - Conference of Deans of Catholic Liberal Arts Colleges on "Christian Culture and Catholic Liberal Education", University of Notre Dame, 1955 (Box 122, Folder 1418)
        - Indiana Council on Religion in Higher Education, 19th Annual State Conference, 1957 (Box 122, Folder 1419)
        - National Conference of Christians and Jews, Inc., Committee on Campus Inter-religious Activities, 1954-1955 (Box 122, Folder 1420)
        - National Consultative Conference on Religion and the State University, University of Michigan: Planning and follow-up, 1958 (Box 122, Folder 1421)
        - National Consultative Conference on Religion and the State University, University of Michigan: Address by H.E. Wornom: "Critical Issues of Religion in Public Education", 1958 (Box 122, Folder 1422)
        - National Consultative Conference on Religion and the State University, University of Michigan: Brochure: "The Teaching of Religion in State Universities", 1958 (Box 123, Folder 1423)
        - Theological Education in America(study directed by H. Richard Niebuhr) Religion programs at specific institutions, 1954-1958 (Box 123, Folder 1424)
      - Religion programs at specific institutions
        - Hillyer College, Hartford, 1955 (Box 123, Folder 1425)
        - Iowa State College, Ames, 1956-1957 (Box 123, Folder 1426)
        - Michigan State University, East Lansing, 1956-1958 (Box 123, Folder 1427)
        - Oklahoma A and M College, Stillwater, 1955-1956 (Box 123, Folder 1428)
        - Pennsylvania State University, University Park, 1955-1957 (Box 123, Folder 1429)
        - Princeton University, 1953 (Box 123, Folder 1430)
        - State University of Iowa, Iowa City, 1961-1963 (Box 123, Folder 1431)
        - University of Illinois, 1956-1957 (Box 123, Folder 1432)
        - University of New Hampshire, 1955
      - General articles
        - (see also: Series III, Wornom Topical Files), 1947-1958, n.d. (Box 123, Folder 1433-1435)
        - Hazen Pamphlets, #1-6, 12 (Box 123, Folder 1436)
  - Kathan era files
    - Consultation planned by R.E.A. Higher Education Committee and Ecology Church Action Project, 1971 (Box 124, Folder 1437-1439)
- Financial and Promotional Records, Series IX
  This series is divided into four sections:
  Financial reports
  Committee records
  Fundraisers
  Funding sources
  - Financial reports
    - Reports, 1935-1966 (Box 125, Folder 1440-1458)
    - Reports, 1967-1978 (Box 126, Folder 1459-1464)
  - Committee records
    - Records, 1930-1949 (Box 126, Folder 1465-1466)
    - Expansion Fund (by state), 1950 (Box 126, Folder 1467-1469)
    - Records, 1950-1951 (Box 127, Folder 1470-1472)
    - Membership Promotion, 1951-1953 (Box 127, Folder 1473)
    - Expansion Fund, 1952 (Box 127, Folder 1474)
    - Records, 1953-1954 (Box 127, Folder 1475-1476)
    - Jewish Laymen Appeals, 1954 (Box 127, Folder 1477)
    - Membership Promotion, 1954 (Box 127, Folder 1478)
    - Protestant Laymen Appeals, 1954 (Box 127, Folder 1479)
    - Catholic/Protestant Appeals, 1954 (Box 127, Folder 1480)
    - Expansion Fund, 1955 (Box 127, Folder 1481)
    - Membership Promotion, 1955 (Box 127, Folder 1482)
    - Jewish Laymen Appeals, 1955 (Box 127, Folder 1483)